{
    "title": "Geography Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following countries does NOT border the Mediterranean Sea?",
            "choices": ["Egypt", "France", "Jordan", "Turkey"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Where is Mount Everest?",
            "choices": ["Bangladesh", "Cambodia", "India", "Nepal"],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following is the name of an independent country?",
            "choices": ["Albania", "Alberta", "America", "Athabaska"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following countries is NOT in South America?",
            "choices": ["Argentina", "Botswana", "Colombia", "Venezuela"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the Great Lakes is wholly contained in the USA?",
            "choices": [
                "Lake Erie",
                "Lake Huron",
                "Lake Michigan",
                "Lake Ontario",
                "Lake Superior"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which country's flag does NOT contain the colour red?",
            "choices": ["Pakistan", "Philippines", "Poland", "Portugal"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What is the former name of Istanbul?",
            "choices": ["Campala", "Carthage", "Constantinople", "Crete"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "The Great Barrier Reef is closest to which country?",
            "choices": ["Australia", "Indonesia", "Japan", "Peru"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following rivers is the longest?",
            "choices": [
                "The Danube River",
                "The Saint Lawrence River",
                "The Volga River",
                "The Yellow River"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Where is the Shwedagon Pagoda?",
            "choices": ["Laos", "Myanmar", "Sri Lanka", "Thailand", "Vietnam"],
            "answer": 1
        }
        
        
    ]
}
